{
    "id": "9eac4264cc934463858ab886259c94b3",
    "title": "Intermediate Level Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He …………………………. the award for his acts of bravery.",
            "description": "We use the simple present tense to talk about facts.",
            "answers": [
                "is deserving",
                "deserves",
                "has deserved"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fd537b7a38814493a7cc3b765b23bb9a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………………… a new generator that saved the company millions.",
            "description": "We use the simple past to talk about finished actions or situations. ",
            "answers": [
                "designed",
                "designs",
                "has designed"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "104e9bec93c544519f5406e3c0903c66"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………………… candy all the time I was dieting.",
            "description": "We use the simple past to talk about finished actions or situations. ",
            "answers": [
                "desire",
                "was desiring",
                "desired"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "43066759b81a4fbebac2850af21b3d91"
        },
        {
            "question": "After the war, the town was a ……………………………… place.",
            "description": "Desolate is the adjective form. Desolated is the past tense of desolate.",
            "answers": [
                "desolate",
                "desolated"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d34f6db967c94eebafe0660d338ebc7e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Many coastal towns were ……………………………………. by the hurricane.",
            "description": "Desolated is the past tense of desolate.",
            "answers": [
                "desolate",
                "desolated",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cd97aa925dea42f982b15503d228d65e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………………….. anyone who is cruel to animals.",
            "description": "We use the simple present to talk about our likes, dislikes, preferences etc.",
            "answers": [
                "despise",
                "am despising",
                "despised"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1b44e2fe86054f669fc42a86156bb6b6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you believe that our destiny is ………………………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "predetermining",
                "predetermined",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ec1a0e07f05f475abf77eb53a4a9f53e"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was the most ……………………………… storm in decades.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "destructive",
                "destructible",
                "destructory"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f52af735480948b796edcc291015f992"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was a desperate criminal on the ..........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lose",
                "loss",
                "loose"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8cafb85b316e4dc18c47a02c46aae56a"
        },
        {
            "question": "How can you forgive such ………………………………. behavior?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "despicable",
                "destitute",
                "despicible"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "eff2964c7c0e4ab0b12fc116c24cbcae"
        },
        {
            "question": "A person of such ……………………………. appetite has no place in our community.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "depraved",
                "depraving",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9be73cbc21b14faaa726602faa2b9950"
        },
        {
            "question": "Inflation has ……………………………….. the country’s currency.",
            "description": "Depreciate means lower the value of.",
            "answers": [
                "depreciated",
                "deprecated",
                "depraved"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cf8fb93512534f1ca0565dffa1ecbf05"
        }
    ]
}